I would like to use this opportunity to
tell you about my dad
that is a strongest man in Uganda he is
a provider and a loving man Emperor
where Trocadero Cola Nokia daddy always
put my needs before his own
because of me sometimes daddy got stuck
because of me sometimes it will speak
the truth
[Music]
until one day daddy discovered that he
did have to do it alone
I am standing in front of you today
because of Daddy's hard work and because
he got up the edges of policy from
Prudential you go through and you save
it's all about love every sacrifice you
make for your children remember you
don't have to do it alone
Prudential listless life together to D
now e